Finding Aid for the Florence Teague Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Florence Teague Collection
1883-1968
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0437
.05 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials related to Florence Teague, and her family. It contains the original 1883 handwritten essay by Mary Summers Conwell, her school certificates, and a newspaper clipping regarding her prize. Florence Teague wrote the family biography.
- Essay
  - 1883
- Family Biography
  - July 23, 1968
- Newspaper Clipping
  - 1883
- Photographs
  - W. F. Tillett
  - Florence N. Conwell (1)
- School Certificates
  - 1882 (3)
  - 1883 (3)